Guide to the Cornell Wordsworth and Cornell Yeats editorial records, 1974-2011.
Cornell Wordsworth and Cornell Yeats editorial records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Wordsworth and Cornell Yeats editorial records, 1974-2011.
6836
Jared R, Curtis 1936-
3 cubic ft.
Computer Media, Microfilm
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Under the general direction of Cornell Professor Emeritus Stephen M. Parrish and the coordination of Jared Curtis, the Cornell Wordsworth edition, begun in 1975, is a series of more than 20 published volumes that provide, for the first time, a complete and accurate record of variant readings, from Wordsworth's earliest drafts to his final lifetime (or posthumous) publication.
The Cornell Yeats edition, begun in 1982, includes 27 volumes of the manuscripts of W. B. Yeats, includiing all extant versions of his poems, as well as his play and other materials.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The Cornell Wordsworth files will eventually include: 7 CD-Rs with master book files and images for The Excursion and Sonnet Series and Itinerary Poems; 1 DVD-R, "Wordsworth's Spots of Time," narrated by Sally Bushell; 28 reels of microfilm with originals submitted to the project; and 12 sets of prints, also submitted to the project by various libraries. Creators include Jared Curtis, and David Garcia. Some items are still held by donor.
The Cornell Yeats files will eventually include: 77 CD-Rs with master files and images for the Yeats volumes; 12 DVD-Rs with images; 25 reels of microfilm with originals submitted to the project; and 8 sets of prints, also submitted to the project. Creators include Jared Curtis, David Garcia, Declan Kiely, David Monahan, Selina Guinness, and various repositories. Some items are still held by donor.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Curtis, Jared R,1936-; Bushell, Sally.; Garcia, David Edward,; Guinness, Selina.; Kiely, Declan.; Monahan, David.; Parrish, Stephen Maxfield.; Wordsworth, William, 1770-1850--Manuscripts.; Wordsworth, William, 1770-1850.; Yeats, W. B.(William Butler), 1865-1939--Manuscripts.; Cornell University Press.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Wordsworth files
CDs and DVDs
Microfilm
Prints
Other files
Yeats files
CDs and DVDs
Microfilm
Prints
Other files
CONTAINER LIST
- Wordsworth files
  - CDs and DVDs
    - Excursion, The, August 22, 2007; 438 (Box 1)
      Master Book files (In Design)
      Editor name: Bushell, Sally; James Butler; Michael Jaye
      Creator of media: Jared Curtis
      ID#: D-WW-0001
    - Excursion, The, August 30, 2007; 439 (Box 1)
      Images for volume
      ID#: D-WW-0002
    - Excursion, The, August 27, 2007; 440 (Box 1)
      Final PDF for printer
      ID#: D-WW-0003
    - Sonnet Series and Itinerary Poems, 1820-1845, July 24, 2002; 441 (Box 1)
      Editor name: Jackson, Geoffrey
      Creator of media: David Garcia
      ID#: D-WW-0004
    - Wordsworth’s Spots of Time, November 14, 2002; 442 (Box 1)
      Streaming Media. Video narrated by Sally Bushell
      Editor name: Bushell, Sally
      Creator of media: Sally Bushell
      ID#: D-WW-0005
    - Excursion, The, September 26, 2005; 443 (Box 1)
      Images for volume: DC MSS. 71, 80
      ID#: D-WW-0006
    - Sonnet Series and Itinerary Poems, 1820-1845, December 3, 2003; 444 (Box 1)
      Master PageMaker files
      ID#: D-WW-0007
    - Sonnet Series and Itinerary Poems, 1820-1845, January 1, 2002; 445 (Box 1)
      Images for volume: Add MS 53544, British Library
      ID#: D-WW-0008
    - Excel lists, January 17, 2009; 446 (Box 1)
      Indices to Wordsworth and Yeats archive.
      Editor name: Curtis, Jared
  - Microfilm
    - Father's Instructions, A: Consisting of Moral Tales, Fables and Reflections, designed to promote the Love of Virtue, a Taste for Knowledge, and an early acquaintance with the Works of Nature, 1781 (Box 2)
      British Library copy
      Editor name: Percival, Thomas
      Creator of media: British Library
      ID#: M-WW-0001
    - Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      Longman printer's copy for Poems, in Two Volumes: British Library, Add MS 47864
      ID#: M-WW-0002
    - Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      Annotated copy of Poems, in Two Volumes (1807), leading to changes in Poems (1815). Yale Univ Beinecke Library (MS Vault / Shelves / Wordsworth)
      Creator of media: Yale
      ID#: M-WW-0003
    - Early Poems and Fragments, 1785-1797, January 1, 1990 (Box 2)
      Christopher Wordsworth's notebook: SpecColl, Northwestern University
      Editor name: Landon, Carol; Curtis, Jared
      Creator of media: Northwestern
      ID#: M-WW-0004
    - Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      Annotated copy of Poetical Works (1836), leading to changes in Poems (1845). Royal Library, Windsor Castle. Pages for Poems, in Two Volumes only
      Creator of media: Royal Library
      ID#: M-WW-0005
    - Last Poems, 1821-1850, January 1, 1993 (Box 2)
      Poems and letters of William Wordsworth, MA 101, Pierpont Morgan Library
      Creator of media: Morgan Library
      ID#: M-WW-0006
    - Fenwick Notes of William Wordsworth, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      Wordsworth's notes dictated to Isabella Fenwick, transcribed by Dora Wordsworth and Edw Quillinan, 1843. Dove Cottage Papers
      Creator of media: Wordsworth Trust
      ID#: M-WW-0007
    - Last Poems, 1821-1850, January 1, 1990 (Box 2)
      Poems Chiefly of Early and Late Years (1842), annotated copy, Univ of Virginia
      Creator of media: University of Virginia
      ID#: M-WW-0008
    - Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      ID#: M-WW-0009
    - Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      Agostino Isola's Pieces Selected from the Italian Poets (Cambridge, 1784), annotated by Wordsworth: Fitzwilliam Museum, Cambridge
      Creator of media: Fitzwilliam Museum
      ID#: M-WW-0010
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 1 (see separate index of reels)
      Editor name: Parrish, Stephen, general editor
      ID#: M-WW-0011
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 2 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0012
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 3 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0013
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 4 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0014
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 5 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0015
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 6 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0016
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 7 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0017
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 8 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0018
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 9 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0019
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 10 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0020
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 11 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0021
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 12 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0022
    - Cornell Wordsworth Series, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MSS, notebooks, and letters of William Wordsworth, Wordsworth Trust, Reel 13 (see separate index of reels)
      ID#: M-WW-0023
    - Early Poems and Fragments, 1785-1797, January 1, 1990 (Box 2)
      MSS of "The Three Graves" in DW's hand; Berg Collection, NYPL
      Creator of media: NYPL
      ID#: M-WW-0024
    - Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807, January 1, 1980 (Box 2)
      MS of Barron Field's "Memoirs of William Wordsworth"; British Library Add MS. 41325
      ID#: M-WW-0025
    - (1) Lyrical Ballads and Other Poems, 1797-1800; (2) Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807, January 1, 1974 (Box 2)
      Lyrical Ballads (1800) revised toward Poems, in Two Volumes (1807); Beinecke Library, Yale University
      Editor name: Butler, James, and Green, Karen (1); Curtis, Jared (2)
      ID#: M-WW-0026.1
    - (1) Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807; (2) Shorter Poems, 1807-1820, January 1, 1974 (Box 2)
      Poems (1815) revised toward Miscellaneous Poems (1820); Beinecke Library, Yale University
      Editor name: Curtis, Jared (1); Ketcham, Carl (2)
      ID#: M-WW-0026.2
    - (1) Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807; (2) Sonnet Series and Itinerary Poems, 1821-1845; (3) Last Poems, 1821-1850, January 1, 1974 (Box 2)
      Sonnets (1838) revised toward Poetical Works (1840); Houghton Library, Harvard University
      Editor name: Curtis, Jared (1 & 3); Geoffrey Jackson (2)
      Creator of media: Harvard
      ID#: M-WW-0027
  - Prints
    - Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807, January 1, 1980 (Box 3)
      Glossy photos for volume. From annotated copy of Poetical Works (1836) in Royal Library, Windsor
      ID#: P-WW-0001
    - Early Poems and Fragments, 1785-1797, June 30, 1994 (Box 3)
      Matte prints of "Imitation of Juvenal" from National Library of Scotland
      Creator of media: National Library of Scotland
      ID#: P-WW-0002
    - Early Poems and Fragments, 1785-1797, June 1, 1994 (Box 3)
      Glossy prints of Christopher Wordsworth's Notebook; Northwestern U. Library
      ID#: P-WW-0003
    - Early Poems and Fragments, 1785-1797, June 1, 1994 (Box 3)
      Matte prints of "Imitation of Juvenal" from Huntington Library & Museum
      Creator of media: Huntington Library
      ID#: P-WW-0004
    - Early Poems and Fragments, 1785-1797, June 1, 1994 (Box 3)
      Glossy prints of "Lesbia" and other translations from British Library
      ID#: P-WW-0005
    - Sonnet Series and Itinerary Poems, 1820-1845, July 28, 1993 (Box 3)
      Matte prints of Ecclesiastical Sonnets in Amherst College Library
      Creator of media: Amherst College Library
      ID#: P-WW-0006
    - Sonnet Series and Itinerary Poems, 1820-1845 (Box 3)
      Glossy photos for volume. From annotated copy of Sonnets (1838) in Dartmouth College Library
      Creator of media: Dartmouth College Library
      ID#: P-WW-0007
    - Excursion, The, January 1, 2000 (Box 3)
      Glossy photos for volume. From the Wordsworth Library, Grasmere
      ID#: P-WW-0008
    - Excursion, The, January 1, 2000 (Box 3)
      ID#: P-WW-0009
    - Poems, in Two Volumes, 1800-1807, May 26, 1975 (Box 3)
      Glossy prints of "The Forsaken" and "Elegiac Verses"; from annotated copy of Poems Chiefly of Early and Late Years (1842), University of Virginia
      ID#: P-WW-0010
    - Last Poems, 1821-1850, January 1, 1990 (Box 3)
      ID#: P-WW-0011
    - Last Poems, 1821-1850, January 1, 1990 (Box 3)
      ID#: P-WW-0012
    - Last Poems, 1821-1850, January 1, 1990 (Box 3)
      Glossy print of "Lyre! Through such power" and "There is a world of spirit" from the Wordsworth Library, Grasmere
      ID#: P-WW-0013
  - Other files
    - "The Cornell Wordsworth: A History", by Jared Curtis, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Wordsworth correspondence, ca. 1964-1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Yeats files
  - CDs and DVDs
    - Excel lists, January 17, 2009; 446 (Box 1)
    - Dreaming of the Bones and Calvary, The, December 11, 2001; 447 (Box 1)
      Images for volume (on image disk for Deirdre)
      Editor name: Wayne K. Chapman
      ID#: D0001.1
    - Deirdre, March 14, 2002; 447 (Box 1)
      Images for volume (on image disk for Chapman)
      Editor name: Virginia Bartholome Rohan
      ID#: D0001.2
    - Deirdre, December 19, 2003; 448 (Box 1)
      Final printer PDF; Master InDesign files and images
      ID#: D0002
    - Dreaming of the Bones and Calvary, The, May 8, 2003; 449 (Box 1)
      ID#: D0003
    - Dreaming of the Bones and Calvary, The, December 7, 2001; 450 (Box 1)
      ID#: D0004
    - In the Seven Woods and The Green Helmet and Other Poems, July 21, 2002; 451 (Box 1)
      Master InDesign files
      Editor name: David Holdeman
      ID#: D0005
    - In the Seven Woods and The Green Helmet and Other Poems, March 13, 1995; 452 (Box 1)
      ID#: D0006
    - Land of Heart’s Desire, The, July 21, 2002; 453 (Box 1)
      Master InDesign files and images
      Editor name: Jared Curtis
      ID#: D0007
    - Land of Heart’s Desire, The, March 1, 2001; 454 (Box 1)
      Images for volume: Add MS 53544, Br Lib
      ID#: D0008
    - Land of Heart’s Desire, The, April 19, 2001; 455 (Box 1)
      Images for volume: Miscellaneous images
      ID#: D0009
    - New Poems, December 5, 2000; 456 (Box 1)
      Final printer PDF; Master PageMaker 6.5 files
      Editor name: J. C. C. Mays and Stephen Parrish
      ID#: D0010
    - New Poems, September 18, 1999; 457 (Box 1)
      Images for volume. Disk formatted as two volumes.
      ID#: D0011
    - Only Jealousy of Emer, The, and Fighting the Waves, March 10, 2005; 458 (Box 1)
      Final printer PDF; Master InDesign files
      Editor name: Steven Winnett
      ID#: D0012
    - Only Jealousy of Emer, The, and Fighting the Waves, September 23, 2003; 459 (Box 1)
      ID#: D0013
    - Only Jealousy of Emer, The, and Fighting the Waves, December 10, 2001; 460 (Box 1)
      Images for volume; raw scans from film
      ID#: D0014
    - Parnell’s Funeral and Other Poems from A Full Moon in March, May 8, 2003; 461 (Box 1)
      Editor name: David R. Clark
      ID#: D0015
    - Parnell’s Funeral and Other Poems from A Full Moon in March, August 9, 2002; 462 (Box 1)
      Images for volume: ATS, Univ. of No. Carolina
      ID#: D0016
    - Responsibilities, March 6, 2003; 463 (Box 1)
      Editor name: William H. O’Donnell
      ID#: D0017
    - Responsibilities, January 17, 2002; 464 (Box 1)
      Images for volume; Word files; sample INDD file
      ID#: D0018
    - Words Upon the Window Pane, The, May 1, 2002; 465 (Box 1)
      Editor name: Mary FitzGerald
      ID#: D0019
    - King’s Threshold, The, August 5, 2002; 1967 (Box 4)
      Images for King’s Threshold and On Baille’s Strand
      Editor name: Declan Kiely
      Creator of media: Declan Kiely
      ID#: D0020.1
    - On Baille’s Strand, August 5, 2002; 1967 (Box 4)
      Images for On Baille’s Strand and King’s Threshold
      ID#: D0020.2
    - King’s Threshold, The, July 23, 2002 (Box 1)
      Images for volume: raw state
      ID#: D0021
    - King’s Threshold, The, December 29, 2003; 468 (Box 1)
      ID#: D0022
    - Deirdre, September 26, 2001; 469 (Box 1)
      Images for volume: raw state, with images for King’s Threshold and Dreaming of the Bones
      Editor name: Virginia Rohan
      ID#: D0023.1
    - King’s Threshold, The, September 26, 2001; 469 (Box 1)
      Images for volume: raw state, with images for Dreaming of the Bones and Deirdre
      ID#: D0023.2
    - Dreaming of the Bones and Calvary, The, September 26, 2001; 469 (Box 1)
      Images for volume: raw state, with images for King’s Threshold and Deirdre
      ID#: D0023.3
    - Parnell’s Funeral and Other Poems from A Full Moon in March, February 18, 2002; 1968 (Box 4)
      Images for volume from Harvard film of White Vellum Notebook
      ID#: D0024.1
    - Deirdre, February 18, 2002; 1968 (Box 4)
      ID#: D0024.2
    - King’s Threshold, The, February 18, 2002; 1968 (Box 4)
      ID#: D0024.3
    - On Baille’s Strand, February 18, 2002; 1968 (Box 4)
      ID#: D0024.4
    - Collaborative One-Act Plays, 1901-1903, August 12, 2006; 471 (Box 1)
      Editor name: James Pethica
      ID#: D0025
    - Collaborative One-Act Plays, 1901-1903, August 12, 2006; 472 (Box 1)
      ID#: D0026
    - King of the Great Clock Tower, The, and a Full Moon in March, December 13, 2005; 473 (Box 1)
      Editor name: Richard Allen Cave
      Creator of media: Richard Cave
      ID#: D0027
    - King of the Great Clock Tower, The, and a Full Moon in March, August 8, 2006; 474 (Box 4)
      Images for volume: SIU 76
      ID#: D0028
    - Tower, The, May 1, 2003; 475 (Box 4)
      Images for volume: Berg
      Editor name: Richard Finneran
      ID#: D0029
    - Diarmuid and Grania, February 10, 2005; 476 (Box 4)
      Editor name: J. C. C. Mays
      ID#: D0030
    - Tower, The, August 28, 2004; 477 (Box 4)
      Images for volume: NLI 13,589
      ID#: D0031
    - Diarmuid and Grania, February 10, 2005; 478 (Box 4)
      ID#: D0032
    - Collaborative One-Act Plays, 1901-1903, August 8, 2006; 479 (Box 4)
      Final printer PDF
      ID#: D0033
    - King’s Threshold, The, June 14, 2005; 480 (Box 4)
      ID#: D0034
    - Tower, The, February 9, 2007; 491 (Box 4)
      ID#: D0035
    - King of the Great Clock Tower, The, and a Full Moon in March, April 5, 2007; 482 (Box 4)
      ID#: D0036
    - Diarmuid and Grania, November 6, 2003; 483 (Box 4)
      Images for volume: Jack Yeats sketches, Berg
      ID#: D0037
    - King of the Great Clock Tower, The, and a Full Moon in March, August 7, 2006; 492 (Box 4)
      Raw images from NLI
      Creator of media: David Monahan, NLI
      ID#: D0038
    - King of the Great Clock Tower, The, and a Full Moon in March, February 20, 2007; 485 (Box 4)
      Image for volume: NLI 30,800 (one page)
      ID#: D0039
    - King of the Great Clock Tower, The, and a Full Moon in March, March 15, 2002; 486 (Box 4)
      Images for volume: Rapallo Nb, Boston College
      ID#: D0040.1
    - Parnell’s Funeral and Other Poems from A Full Moon in March, March 15, 2002; 486 (Box 4)
      ID#: D0040.2
    - Wordsworth MS, March 15, 2002; 486 (Box 4)
      Sonnet Sequences: Royal Library, Windsor
      Editor name: Geoffrey Jackson
      ID#: D0040.3
    - Collaborative One-Act Plays, 1901-1903, July 30, 2005; 487 (Box 4)
      Images for volume: Berg, The Travelling Man, The Shanachie
      ID#: D0041
    - Collaborative One-Act Plays, 1901-1903, August 15, 2005; 488 (Box 4)
      Images for volume: Berg, The Travelling Man
      ID#: D0042
    - Sophocles’ Oedipus at Colonus, December 20, 2006; 493 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: NLI: Disk 1
      ID#: D0043
    - Sophocles’ Oedipus at Colonus, December 20, 2006; 494 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: NLI: Disk 2
      ID#: D0044
    - Sophocles’ Oedipus at Colonus, October 9, 2007; 491 (Box 4)
      Images for volume: NLI 8767(2), 2r (reveals palimpsest)
      ID#: D0045
    - Sophocles’ Oedipus at Colonus, October 9, 2007; 495 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: NLI: Disk 3
      ID#: D0046
    - Sophocles’ Oedipus at Colonus, March 25, 2005; 493 (Box 4)
      Images of 1st edn, London, 1934. Lib. Congress copy
      Creator of media: Library of Congress
      ID#: D0047
    - Sophocles’ Oedipus at Colonus, May 19, 2006; 494 (Box 4)
      Images for volume: raw state; HRC (U. of Texas at Austin)
      Creator of media: HRC, U of T
      ID#: D0048
    - Tower, The, June 5, 2005; 496 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: NLI: NLI 13,589 (1-3, 25-32)
      ID#: D0049
    - Tower, The, June 5, 2005; 497 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: NLI: NLI 13,589 (17–25)
      ID#: D0050
    - Tower, The, May 15, 2005; 498 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: NLI: NLI 13,589 (5-16)
      ID#: D0051
    - Tower, The, April 23, 2005; 499 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: NLI: NLI 13,589 (3 & 4)
      ID#: D0052
    - Tower, The, August 19, 2005; 500 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: NLI: NLI Mss 30,373; 36,285; 21,870; 30,540; 30,865; 30,760; 30,413; 30, 757; 21,858; 30,358; 12,583; 13586(12)
      ID#: D0053
    - Tower, The, October 28, 2005; 500 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: parts of NLI 21,870; 13,583; 30,540; 13,589(26)2
      ID#: D0054
    - Introduction to plays, March 20, 2007; 1969 (Box 4)
      Images: raw state: NLI 13,571; 13,572
      ID#: D0055.1
    - Where There Is Nothing, March 20, 2007; 1969 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: NLI 30,303 (Wade 41)
      ID#: D0055.2
    - Sophocles’ Oedipus at Colonus, October 29, 2007; 502 (Box 4)
      Raw images for volume: Add Ms 55003; corresp. & scores
      ID#: D0056
    - Correspondence: WBY-Macmillan, 1932-1939, November 27, 2007; 1970 (Box 4)
      Raw images: correspondence
      ID#: D0057
    - Correspondence: WBY-Macmillan, 1935-1939, January 10, 2008; 1971 (Box 4)
      Raw images: correspondence; scores for several plays
      ID#: D0058
    - White Vellum Notebook, February 22, 2005; 1972 (Box 4)
      Images from microfilm at Harvard
      ID#: D0059
    - Sophocles’ Oedipus at Colonus, September 12, 2008; 490 (Box 4)
      ID#: D0060
    - Golden Helmet, The, and The Green Helmet, June 13, 2008; 1973 (Box 8)
      Raw images from NLI: NLI 1731; NLI 8761
      Editor name: William Hogan
      ID#: D0061
    - Golden Helmet, The, and The Green Helmet, May 11, 2008; 1974 (Box 8)
      Raw images from Macmillan Archive: BL(2)
      ID#: D0062
    - On Baille’s Strand, August 22, 2005; 1975 (Box 8)
      Raw images for volume: NLI 30,331
      ID#: D0063
    - On Baille’s Strand, June 28, 2006; 1976 (Box 8)
      Images for volume: raw state: HRC
      ID#: D0064
    - At the Hawk’s Well and The Cat and the Moon, June 18, 2008; 1977 (Box 8)
      Images: Correspondence Macmillan Archive
      Editor name: Andrew Parkin
      ID#: D0065
    - At the Hawk’s Well and The Cat and the Moon, June 20, 2008; 1978 (Box 8)
      Images for volume: Add MSS 55878, 55884, 55891
      ID#: D0066
    - At the Hawk’s Well and The Cat and the Moon, March 5, 2007; 1979 (Box 8)
      Raw images for volume: NLI Disk #1
      ID#: D0067
    - At the Hawk’s Well and The Cat and the Moon, March 5, 2007; 1980 (Box 8)
      Raw images for volume: NLI Disk #2
      ID#: D0068
    - At the Hawk’s Well and The Cat and the Moon, March 5, 2007; 1981 (Box 8)
      Raw images for volume: NLI Disk #3
      ID#: D0069
    - At the Hawk’s Well and The Cat and the Moon, May 19, 2008; 1982 (Box 8)
      Images for volume: HRC
      ID#: D0070
    - White Vellum Notebook, February 22, 2005; 1983 (Box 8)
      Images from microfilm at Harvard, Part 1
      ID#: D0071
    - White Vellum Notebook, February 22, 2005; 1984 (Box 8)
      Images from microfilm at Harvard, Part 2
      ID#: D0072
    - White Vellum Notebook, February 22, 2005; 1985 (Box 8)
      Images from microfilm at Harvard, Part 3
      ID#: D0073
    - King of the Great Clock Tower, The, and a Full Moon in March, March 20, 2007; 1986 (Box 8)
      Images for volume: NLI Rapallo Nb; contains introduction to play and fragment of dialogue from Resurrection
      ID#: D0074.1
    - Resurrection, The, March 20, 2007; 1986 (Box 8)
      Images for volume: NLI Rapallo Nb; contains fragment of dialogue from Resurrection and introduction to The King of the Great Clock Tower
      Editor name: Selina Guinness
      ID#: D0074.2
    - Resurrection, The, October 14, 2006; 1987 (Box 8)
      ID#: D0075
    - Resurrection, The, April 18, 2006; 1988 (Box 8)
      ID#: D0076.1